hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Kowski and in this podcast we
talk about ways for you to grow in your
life your business to reach more clients
and to have the kind of coaching or
online course business that you've
always wanted now I've been in the
online course business space for over 21
years and I've helped some of the top
mentors in the world scale their
businesses to over tens of millions of
dollars I've personally built multiple
coaching businesses over $10 million a
year in profit and that's what I want to
help you with is how to do that in your
own business whether you're just getting
started and growing your email this is
the number one thing that you absolutely
must be doing Bar None email is not dead
we use social media to attract people to
find the right people we use podcasts to
help nurture we use YouTube to help
connect with messaging with people we
have trainings that deliver value to
people and sell our programs but our
email list is where it all kind of
connects together maybe you found this
through my email list I actually have an
email list to people join through
different trainings and things that
we've done and I send links to our
videos and our podcast and different
things that we offer through that to
people the reason why you want to grow
your email list is this and again you
may be like well I don't open every
email that I get that's true and that's
why you want to be emailing your list
consistently that's why you don't want
to just email it once a week because the
chances of you actually having somebody
open something from you once or twice a
week very low but if you're cons
consistently sending value multiple
times a week I would even urge you to
say you can email your list twice a day
and it's okay if you're delivering value
if it's not just Spam if it's not just
you selling stuff but you actually say
hey I got this video here that's got
this training hey here's a little nugget
for you that could help you and that
nurtures trust and relationship with
people now not everybody's going to want
to read those emails but the ones who do
and the ones who stick around and the
ones who actually listen to you those
are the ones who are celebrating you and
you're celebrating them and it's
building connection and community and it
becomes this beautiful thing that you
all get to come together around and it
makes this amazing experience that
everybody loves to be a part of and so
to grow our email list there's a number
of different ways that we do this number
one it's real simple if you just tell
people you have an email list they can
join you know if you go to my site
Jeremiah Kowski decom there's literally
a newsletter join button on there I I
actually should probably just put a page
together that says Hey listen if you
want to get some you know pieces like my
latest updates pieces of advice
trainings I send trainings out every
single week join the email list I I
probably should do that I actually just
saw a guy do that recently that's
another way to grow your email list if
you have trainings consistently that you
send out like I do I don't know why I
haven't done that another one could be a
freebie I have a freebie it's a chat GPT
prompt download I'm going to show it to
you here real quick if you go over to my
website you can find this it's got some
of my best prompts that I've been using
and we've been using to create sales
copy and messaging and and help us with
our courses and our trainings right here
over at my website 8 figure chat GPT
prompts right here download the ultimate
prompt document you can type in your
email address you can get access to it
instantly right there download the
document and it's a Google doc that you
can access we have people who are
accessing it every single day to be able
to do this by the way chat GPT now is
free and so anybody can use these
prompts to help them in their business
to grow and to brainstorm a lot of
incredible ideas for their offers okay
so that's one thing you could literally
just have a Google doc be a download
that you can give somebody that doesn't
take a lot to create some of yall are
like oh I need to create an ebook no you
could literally just make a Google doc
that you could share with somebody and
that's your download we got to stop
overthinking it you know the value that
we deliver you don't want to try to
deliver when we're growing our email
list this big massive transformation
that's going to change people's lives
that's what comes later in their in your
coaching program but you deliver one key
element of what's going to solve a
problem for them maybe it helps them
figure out an idea for a course or an
idea for a business or an idea for an
email list videos like this are another
great example by the way if you're
looking for ideas for freebies to give
away this is a strategy I tell all my
clients it's huge YouTube is your number
one resource for searching for ideas for
freebies let me explain the most post
viewed YouTube videos on any specific
topic and you can start to search in
YouTube for different topics let's let's
in just go here right now and let's do
this live while I'm talking about this
if I go over to YouTube and I type in
okay uh how to price your coaching
program okay I was actually looking that
up earlier not a ton of well that one's
got 67,000 views let's click on that and
then let's see what's on the sidebar
here creating your first coaching
program what to say when clients say
your price is too high how to design
your coaching package okay that might be
even better than how to price your
program in fact think of it this way two
offers how to price your coaching
program or how to design your first
coaching package which one sounds a
little more appealing definitely the
second one and you can see right
here by the amount of views that this
video has
gotten that that's actually a really
great topic I'm going actually going to
subscribe to her Channel because you
know what that's a really great um great
great key there I Can Tell She's Got
some great energy going on here she's
got a lot of really good content I have
never heard of her before but I'm I'm
already a fan just by the the vibe that
I'm picking up just by watching this
right there okay and so all that to say
is that those are great ways to come up
with ideas for freebies and again it
might not be the first video you click
this first video here okay was one idea
and you can notice a lot of these
haven't even crack 10,000 views I try to
find things that have a little bit more
than the 10,000 views but if you click
on a video go look at if you're on your
computer what's on the
sidebar and you will find ideas that are
related to your Niche how to become a
health coach from scratch right here
again that's another great topic that
you could literally create a freebie
around right there is guiding people
through that process this whole video is
like a master class on what you could
create a freebie around and and then you
could teach something similar to that
okay so another thing that you can do
another thing that you can you can offer
is it can either be a a document or it
could be a video training for a freebie
to grow your email list it could be a
pod an audio recording a
podcast um it could be a video recording
it could be a video training one thing
that we are finding is a lot of people
are wanting on demand instant access
versus having to wait time for stuff
okay now I'm a big fan of Hosting as our
lead magnets Live Events and even
webinars and I think it's a great way to
build trust with people because you're
requiring them to show up at a specific
time but here's how I like to use that
now is what we're finding is that a lot
of people their attention span is a lot
lower so if we can deliver value in a
free way to get people on our email list
watching YouTube content watching video
content and they can get instant access
to stuff that instant gratification
triggers something in people's minds
that if they are the right qualified
process ECT you can then retarget them
with something that's live and that's
where you can make a good sales
presentation that's where you can
actually deliver a better sales
presentation so you don't sell a lot on
your email list stuff on your lead
magnet you don't do like a hard sell on
that you can mention what you have for
sale you can give them an opportunity
but your goal is not to Hard Sell the
goal is to continue to nurture that
trust with them as far as that goes you
still want to give them an opportunity I
would say today to to sign up with you
you don't want to make it to where
people have to wait um but you want to
also create some urgency as well maybe
expiring bonuses maybe some free offers
things like that a great way to word
that could be this is the lowest price
it will ever be uh this is only
guaranteed until this day I like that
language because a you could move the
guarantee up if you want to uh and it's
and it's also honest and has some
Integrity behind that language as far as
that way cuz you're only guaranteeing
that these freebies are going to be
offered during that time you're only
guaranteeing that the price is going to
be up to that time as far as that goes
okay so again to grow your email list
it's something of value that you're
delivering to people how do we figure
out what those things are of value that
we can deliver to people well here's
what I look for so I look for what is
the transformation that I deliver to my
main clients and then what my goal is is
to actually listen to what are they
wanting from me now another great way to
do it is you can also look at again like
I said YouTube videos great way to find
topics for freebies really is it's where
I find a lot of them that's where I
recommend a lot of my clients find the
topics to see what those YouTube video
titles
are but you can also look at who in your
Niche what freebies are your Niche using
and now a lot of people are attaching
their freebies to their YouTube videos
so you could also go deeper in the
YouTube journey and look at across
somebody's Channel what are their most
recent videos and then what is the
freebie that they're giving to their
Market
you can put your own spin on that topic
of the freebie and find that let's take
a look here at at a at a I'm just going
to just blindly go find somebody's
freebie off of a YouTube that we could
look at in fact let's look right
here what what she has right here oh
look it free blueprint for Breaking Free
from 9 to
5 this is the lady that I just subscribe
to right now free blueprint for Breaking
Free from 9: to
5 so you can get instant access to this
PDF right
here by by by typing in your info I'm
going to I'm going to just type it in
just to just to kind of
see
okay and oh look at this want my
strategy so check your inbox here it is
want my strategy yes reserve my seat now
and so what she's using is she has the
PDF freebie which is low commitment but
then number
two oh that button doesn't seem to
working oh here we go so it's a
webinar that gives you a full framework
and you can watch this webinar after you
grab that freebie four-step framework to
go from employee to entrepreneur again
that's another great way to do it where
she had the PDF freebie right here to
grow the email list but then immediately
gives you an
invitation to go through with a longer
form training that's another great way
to do it where you can give them an
additional secondary offer after the PDF
freebie to watch a longer form piece of
content with you and I find that that
works really well as well so again
delivering value whatever your offer is
whatever your Niche is whatever your
topic is you can deliver value to people
to grow your email list and then you
want to be emailing your list with value
consistently always looping back to in
your longer form messaging whether it be
YouTube content whether it be webinars
whether it be video trainings
always looping forward to the fact that
you have a program that you'd love to
see them join that they can either apply
with you they can book a call with you
or like my program they can just jump in
by taking advantage of a free trial with
us and again I'd love to work with you
as far as that goes if you're a coach if
you're a mentor if you're a trainer if
you're somebody who's looking to grow
your email list you're looking to to
accelerate yourself my client growth
accelerator program we actually offer a
14-day trial that you can jump in on
that to try it out to check it out and
become a client of ours we have some
free courses that we give you as well
for jumping into that just to say thank
you um that are yours to keep forever
just for becoming a part of that client
growth accelerator program so again I'd
love to see you in there I'd love to
work with you further in my accelerator
program and start to get you more
results in your business faster all
right we'll talk to you soon have a good
one everybody bye
[Music]